O-Okay, Ross, I realize
that you didn't expect
to walk in and see that,
but let me explain, okay?
We weren't
doing anything!
Rach, he just saw us.
Shh...
But what you saw,
that is the extent of it, okay?
One kiss.
No, come on.
That is a lie.
We also kissed
in Barbados.
Dude, chill!
Okay, we also kissed
in Barbados,
but we didn't
plan it, okay?
And the only reason that
that happened was-was
because I saw you
kissing Charlie.
Yeah, you started it!
I have got to chill!
Look, we-we probably
should've talked
to you about this
before it ever
happened... but...
Oh, we feel so terrible
about this, Ross.
Yeah, but it
did... happen.
So...
Ross?
Can we just
close the door?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Ross, say something...
anything.
So, you two are...?
Yeah.
And have you... had...?
No, no.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
But if I hadn't walked
in here, would you...?
Probably...
No! No.
Ross, this is not
how we wanted you
to find out about this.
You have every
right to go nuts.
I'm not going nuts.
Do you see me going nuts?
No, but... you
know what I mean.
Hey, hey, hey.
( laughing )
If you two are happy,
then I'm happy for you.
I'm fine!
Really?
Absolutely.
( squeaky ):
I'm fine!
Totally fine.
( laughing ):
I don't know why it's coming out
all loud and squeaky,
'cause really...
( deep-pitched ):
I'm fine.
I'm not saying I wasn't
a little surprised...
to... see you
guys kissing.
I mean, at first I was
like... ( screams )
...but now that I've
had time to absorb it...
loving this.
Ross...
It's all working out.
Me and Charlie, and you two.
You know what
we should do?
Calm ourselves?
No...
We should all have dinner.
Yes, we'll do it tomorrow night.
I'll cook!
Wow, uh, look,
don't-don't you think
that'll be a little weird?
Weird? What? What's weird?
The only thing weird would be
if someone didn't like
Mexican food
because I'm making fajitas!
I do like fajitas.
Oh, God, this adoption
stuff is so overwhelming.
There's intercountry adoption,
dependency adoption.
There's so many
ways to go
and this is, like,
the biggest decision
of our lives.
There's a hair
in my coffee.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Hey, have you
seen Frank Junior?
'Cause he's meeting me
here with the triplets.
You know, it's funny,
every time you say "triplets,"
I immediately think of three
hot, blond, 19-year-olds.
That's sweet.
Drink your hair.
Hey, what's all this stuff?
Oh, they're brochures from
different adoption agencies.
Ooh, babies.
Oh, this one is so cute.
Get this one.
That's not really
how it works.
Oh, how does it work?
I don't know!
Well, if you're having
a hard time,
you should talk to my friends,
Bill and Pauline.
They adopted a kid.
I'm sure they'd help you.
MONICA:
Thanks, that would be great.
Yeah.
Hey, honey, wouldn't
that be great?
( gagging )
All right, all right, all right,
remember what we talked about.
When we're in a public place,
there are certain rules.
( screaming )
Those aren't
the rules!
Hi.
It's good
to see you.
It's good to see you, too.
Hi. Hi.
How you doing?
They've all gotten so big.
Which one is which again?
Oh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
that's, uh, Frank Junior, Jr.
pulling the tampons
out of the lady's purse.
And, uh, that's,
uh, Chandler
playing around Chandler.
And, uh, that's Leslie
throwing bagels on him.
"Willing to
adopt triplets?"
No.
Uh, can I just say I know
we're doing this for Ross
and that's cool,
but if it was up to me,
this is not what we'd be doing
on our first date.
Well, what would we be doing?
I'd take you out
for a romantic night--
some champagne,
fancy dinner...
feel you up
on the carriage ride home.
Feel me up?
In a carriage.
Hey, Charlie.
Hi.
So... dreading this?
Oh, you bet.
So, did you, uh, bring
a little something for Ross?
Actually, uh, it's some stuff
you left at my apartment.
Oh. Oh.
Thanks.
And you know, you can just give
me my stuff whenever you want.
Yeah, I didn't throw
any of that out.
( squeaky ):
I thought I heard voices.
What...?
Hi, Charlie.
Hey, Joey.
Well, hey.
And, uh... oh, you're going
to have to introduce me
to your new girlfriend.
( laughing )
I'm just kidding.
I know Rachel.
I know.
( grunting indistinctly )
Come.
Please, come in, come in.
Okay. Uh, well,
we brought you some wine.
Oh...
That is so thoughtful.
She's a keeper.
( laughing )
Oh, and what did you bring me,
huh?
Uh, actually,
that's, uh...
Underwear, a toothbrush
and a Van Halen CD.
I can use all these things!
Gosh, Ross, you know,
you seem a little, uh...
What? Fine?
Because I am.
Huh? Aren't you?
Aren't you? Aren't...?
Who-Who else is fine?
Come on.
Okay, listen, hey, Ross,
why don't you, uh,
try to relax, okay?
Maybe have a drink.
You know what?
That is a very good idea.
I'm going to go make
a pitcher of margaritas.
Oh, God...
So adorable.
Look at them sleeping
there like angels.
Yeah, I really cherish
these moments,
'cause, uh...
before you know it,
they're going
to be awake again.
Well... they may be a handful,
but they're so cute.
Yeah.
Oh, God, last time
I baby-sat them,
they did the
funniest thing.
I haven't slept
in four years.
That's a long time.
You just don't know
how hard it is, Phoebe.
There's just so many of them.
You know, two I could handle.
Two's great.
You just hold one
in each hand.
But what do I do
when the third one runs at me
with his bike helmet on?
I got no more hands
to protect my area.
There's three of them,
Phoebe, three.
Yeah, I know, Frank.
I counted them when they
were coming out of my area.
Sometimes I think that I...
Oh, no, no, no,
I can't say it.
It's too horrible, no.
What?
( mumbling ):
No, no, I can't.
Oh, my God, Frank,
are you thinking of leaving?
Because I didn't have
those triplets
so you could
just run out on them.
Oh, no, I would
never do that. No.
I just was thinking
that, you know,
maybe you could take one.
What?!
You can't separate them.
That's terrible.
Which one?
Thank you so much
for seeing us.
Phoebe has told us
such great things
about you guys.
Oh, please,
we're happy to help.
We went through the same thing
when we were adopting.
So, a lot of malfunctioning
wee-wees and hoo-hoos
in this room, huh?
I mean, you have a lovely home.
Well, we appreciate
anything you can tell us.
Well, actually,
I think this might help.
It's pretty much
all the information you need.
Oh, my God.
Everything is broken down
into categories
and then cross-referenced...
and then color-coded
to correspond
with the forms in the back.
Thank you.
I think I just had
a tiny orgasm.
I know the process
is frustrating,
but it's so worth it.
Adopting Owen was the best thing
that ever happened to us.
That's great.
Can I see the book?
You want me to wash my
hands first, don't you?
Well, it's just so pretty
and white.
Bathroom is down the hall
to your left.
I would've told
him to do it, too.
Can I adopt you?
Hey, you must be Owen.
Yeah.
I'm Chandler.
Hey, I was in the Scouts, too.
You were?
Yeah. In fact,
my father was a den mother.
Huh?
You know how to use a compass?
I have a badge in it.
You do?
That's fantastic.
You want to see it?
I'd love to, but I got to get
back to talking your parents.
They're telling us all about
how they adopted you.
What?
I'm adopted?
I got nothing.
Well, that first
batch of margaritas
was not so great,
but this second batch
is good.
Well, maybe the next batch,
we could all get some.
Oh, God, this is fun,
isn't it, you know?
Just the four us,
just hanging.
Dude, are you okay?
And when are the fajitas
going to be ready?
I'm fine, okay?
I'm great.
I'm just, I'm just
proud of us, you know?
There's no weirdness,
no tension.
No awareness.
You know, we make
a great foursome.
We should do more
stuff together.
( gasps )
Let's take a trip.
Okay, where
do you think
we-we can go?
( dinging )
My fajitas!
Look, Charlie.
I just want you to know,
Ross is just having
a little trouble
adjusting to the thought
of Joey and me.
You know, he normally
doesn't drink like this.
Oh, you know what,
this is nothing.
My father is a raging alcoholic.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Have I made this evening
uncomfortable?
Fajitas!
Be careful, very hot plate.
Very hot.
Ross, you don't even
have oven mitts on.
( chuckles )
That is going to hurt tomorrow.
Okay, well,
this is crazy.
We can't seriously be talking
about me taking
one of your kids, can we?
Oh, no, of course we're not.
It's insane.
I know.
Alice would never go for it,
right?
I don't know.
She's pretty tired, too.
I think we could get her
on board.
Well, just, you know,
for argument's sake,
you know, hypothetically,
which one would you
be willing to give up?
Huh...
Frank Junior Jr.
Uh, you'd be getting
a really good one.
I mean,
you know, he's really funny.
Like, the other day,
he made up this joke.
What's green and says,
"Hey, I'm a frog"?
( laughs ):
A talking frog.
Oh, no, you can't have him.
He's too funny.
Well, all right, that's fine.
What about, um, Leslie?
Oh, no, no, not Leslie, no.
She's, she's the only one that
knows how to burp the alphabet.
All right,
so that leaves Chandler.
Oh, no, you
can't have Chandler.
No, no, no, no.
She's my little
genius.
I got big hopes for her.
She's going to be a doctor
or... Realtor.
Wow, Frank, I think
we just ran out of kids.
Oh, I think you're right.
Oh, wow.
Phoebe, I don't think
I can give one of them up.
I mean, you know,
they drive me crazy,
but they're my babies.
I'm sorry, Frank, I didn't
realize things were so bad.
You know, I'll help out more.
I can baby-sit
any time you want.
You name the day
and I'll be there.
How 'bout tomorrow?
Well, that's not good.
But,
you know,
I can move some stuff around
and I'll be there.
You and Alice just take
the whole day together.
You'd do that for us?
Are you kidding?
That's what sisters are for.
Oh...
Oh, look at them.
I love you
so much.
Oh, crap, don't wake up.
Don't wake up.
Where are Bill
and Colleen?
They're in the kitchen
getting us something to eat.
Can you believe
how nice they are?
We have to leave.
Why?
What did you do in the bathroom?
I didn't get
to the bathroom.
I bumped into Owen
on the way,
and he didn't know
he was adopted.
And there's a slight chance
I may have told him.
Oh, my God.
Where's my purse?
No, you know what, I can
replace everything in there.
Get that binder and let's go.
Hey.
BILL:
Some little snacks
for everybody.
Oh, you don't have
to eat the sour worms.
Those are for Owen.
COLLEEN:
I'll go get him
in a second.
By the way,
you should know,
we haven't told him
he's adopted yet.
But kids are so intuitive.
Don't you think on some
level he already knows?
I'm adopted?!
See, intuitive.
What?
Where did you
hear that?
He told me.
And he paid me $50
not to tell.
Which technically now
you should give back.
You told him he's adopted?
I'm so sorry,
but you should have
a sign out there
or something.
Or at least whisper
it to people
when they
come in the door.
( whispering ):
Owen doesn't know
he's adopted.
And he also thinks
Santa is real.
He isn't?
We have to get out
of here, baby.
Everyone, I would like
to make a toast.
To Rachel and Joey.
Oy.
And...
to love.
Ah, love.
L-O-V-E, love.
"L" is for life.
And what is life
without love?
Oh, my God.
Are we supposed to answer?
"O" is for...
"Oh, wow."
The "V" is for this very
surprising turn of events.
Which I am still fine with,
by the way.
( screeching ):
"E..."
is for how extremely normal
I find it
that you two...
are together.
And that one day
you might get married.
And have children of your own.
Dude, are you okay?
Totally.
Ross, you don't seem okay.
I'm sorry. It must be
the pressure of entertaining.
I think everyone would feel
better if we had some flan.
Wait, Ross.
Ross, I, um, I have to take off.
No.
I'm sorry.
I have a really early
class in the morning.
This has been lovely.
Wasn't it?
And you thought it would
be awkward with Joey,
and that you never
really liked Rachel.
You are on fire.
I'll call you
in the morning, okay?
Okay.
All right.
Oh, God, Rachel, what Ross
just said, this is just...
Oh, that's okay.
Girls tend not to like me.
Bye.
Okay, I guess
it's just flan for three.
Hey... hey, that rhymes.
You know what, Ross?
I think we're going
to take off, too.
Oh, oh...
of course.
God, I'm so stupid.
You guys are a couple now.
I mean, you probably
just want to be alone.
No, no, it's just
it's getting late...
Hey, hey, hey.
It's fine.
It's totally fine.
I've got plenty of margaritas.
It's all good.
( dinging )
I don't even know
what that's for.
You know what?
I think I'm going
to stay here
and make sure he's okay.
Yeah, that's probably
a good idea.
Just, I'll see you
in the morning.
Uh-huh. Okay.
Hey, you know, Joey,
I don't think he's ever
going to be okay with this.
Doesn't look good, does it?
JOEY:
Morning.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Did you, you stay
here all night?
Yeah.
So you took off
my pants and shoes?
No, no, no, no.
You actually did that
when you were dancing
to the Chicago soundtrack.
Look, uh, Ross, about,
about Rachel and I.
Listen, you don't have
to worry about that, okay,
because nothing's going
to happen.
What do you mean?
Well, she and I said
from the beginning
that we weren't
going to do anything
unless you were okay with it.
And clearly...
What are you talking about?
I'm fine.
It's okay, Ross.
You know, I, I totally
understand.
Of course you're
not fine.
You're...
You're Ross and Rachel.
Yeah, except we're not.
I mean, we haven't been
a couple in, like...
six years.
Oh, my God,
is that right?
Has it been that long?
That's what I hear, yeah.
This is crazy.
I mean, six years,
and because of me
you guys aren't
going to be together?
Can I ask you
something?
Really, what...
what is this thing
with you and Rachel?
Come on, I mean,
you know me.
( chuckling ):
You know...
Joey.
I'm crazy about her.
And she feels
the same way?
I think so.
Well, then, maybe it's
time we all moved on.
Yeah, but, Ross, I mean,
you're not okay with it.
No, but...
I want to be.
And, hey, I will be.
Besides, I'm with
Charlie, right?
Oh, my God.
I'm still with Charlie,
aren't I?
I mean, she didn't see
the dance, did she?
No, no, no.
No, that was, uh,
that was just for me.
Are you, uh,
are you sure about this?
Yeah, I'm sure.
And... we're okay?
( chuckles )
( gasps )
Hey, Pheebs,
um, we just want to
give you a heads-up.
Bill and Colleen hate us.
Owen didn't know
he was adopted
and Monica told him.
What?
Still, he had
to find out sometime.
Yeah, but how would
you like it
if someone told the triplets
that you gave birth to them?
I'm going to go tell Emma
she was an accident.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org